

LÊ KHÁNH VÂN

OBJECTIVES

With the knowledge about Software Testing learned from Funix center, I hope to develop myself in a professional working environment and become an excellent employee in the near future.

From 1 – 2 months: Integrate well with the environment, well apply learned knowledge in practice

From 3 – 6 months: Become a junior tester From 2 - 3 years : Become a senior tester

**** 0862210540



khanhvan.9500@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Gender : Female

Birthday : 07/06/1995

Marital status : Single

Nationality : Vietnamese

Country : Vietnam

Address : Ha Dong District, Ha Noi, Vietnam

CAREER INFORMATION

Level : Non - Experienced

Salary : Negotiable Job type : Full time

Industry : IT - Software

Location : Ha Noi

EXPERIENCE

Year(s) of Experience: Under 1 year

Current Level: Experienced (Non - Manager)



11/2021 - 3/2022: Funix Center - A member of FPT Corporation **Tester course**

Complete 4 certificates:

- Software Testing (create test cases, test report, record bugs, ...)
- Database Systems (SQL server, practice SQL statements, ...)
- Introduction to Software Engineering (SRS document, diagrams, ...)
- Mastering your computer (software, hardware, internet, ...)

4/2021 - 8/2021: HR Executive - P. Dussmann Vietnam Co., Ltd

- Recruiting personnel for Hanoi branch
- Timekeeping, salary calculation for employees
- In charge of work related to social insurance for employees
- In charge of the input procedures for new employees
- Drafting labor contracts, tracking and maintaining employee records

5/2020 - 4/2021: Sales Admin - SVC TRADING AND TECHNICAL SERVICE JSC

- Creat purchase orders, contracts for customers
- Provide document related to sales, store customer database and sales documents.
- Order and delivery goods to the customer
- Prepare certificates of origin and quality upon delivery.
- Execute reports upon request from manager

5/2017 - 4/2020: Sale Support - Bach Khoa Solar Energy Development And Investment Joint Stock Company

- Report of Business plan of Hanoi branch
- Create purchase orders, contracts for customers and distributors.
- Provide document related to sales, store customer database and sales documents.
- Order and delivery goods to distributors

GITHUB & PROJECT

Test report & bugs list:

https://github.com/khanhvan95/CV_Le_Khanh_Van

EDUCATION

Highest Degree Level: Bachelor

Completion date 7-2017

Bachelor - University of Economics and Law (National University of Ho Chi Minh City)

Major: International Trade Law

SKILLS

*** Teamwork skill Communication skill *** ***

Office software skill Time management skill

Analysis and reporting skill

SQL server

Redmine server

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese - Intermediate

English - Intermediate

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

Excellent staff of month

Excellent staff of year 2018